Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition UP209
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition
1982 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
UP209
0.5 Linear Feet
13 Digital Object(s)
9.8 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized chronologically into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the bulletin of the School of Nutrition. It describes the graduation requirements for degrees from that school, as well as programs of study, faculty listing, financial aid available, and other information for perspective students.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts School of Nutrition Science and Policy was established in 1981 and renamed the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy in 2001. Its mission is to improve the nutritional health and well-being of populations throughout the world.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
- Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1982 -- 2020; 1982 -- 1998; UP209.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 13 Digital Object(s); 9.8 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the bulletin of the School of Nutrition. It describes the graduation requirements for degrees from that school, as well as programs of study, faculty listing, financial aid available, and other information for perspective students.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically by format.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1982 -- 1983; UP209.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1983 -- 1984; UP209.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1984 -- 1985; UP209.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1985 -- 1986; UP209.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1986 -- 1987; UP209.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1987 -- 1988; UP209.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1988 -- 1989; UP209.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1989 -- 1990; UP209.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1991 -- 1993; UP209.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 1997 -- 1998; UP209.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Nutrition, 2003; UP209.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Nutrition Course Bulletin, Fall 2014; UP209.000024; 1 Digital Object(s); 592 Kilobytes
    Nutrition Course Bulletin for the Fall 2014 semester.
  - Nutrition Course Bulletin, Spring 2015; UP209.000025; 1 Digital Object(s); 611 Kilobytes
    Nutrition Course Bulletin for the Spring 2015 semester.
  - Nutrition Course Bulletin, Fall 2015; UP209.000026; 1 Digital Object(s); 609 Kilobytes
    Nutrition Course Bulletin for the Fall 2015 semester.
  - Nutrition Course Bulletin, Spring 2016; UP209.000027; 1 Digital Object(s); 664 Kilobytes
    Nutrition Course Bulletin for the Spring 2016 semester.
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2016; UP209.001.00003; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.7 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2016
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2016, accession 2017.022.
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2017; UP209.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.74 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2017
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2017, accession UP-2018-012.
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2017; UP209.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.78 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2017
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP209.001.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.74 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2018
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2018, accession UP-2018-033.
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP209.001.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.61 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2019; UP209.001.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.81 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2019
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP209.000022; 612 Kilobytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Fall 2019
  - Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2020; UP209.000023; 1.47 Megabytes
    Nutrition Bulletin, Spring 2020
  - Nutrition Course Bulletin, Fall 2020; UP209.000028; 1.5 Megabytes
    Nutrition Course Bulletin, Fall 2020